Possess them all.
Annabelle Comes Home is a horror film directed by Gary Dauberman.
Determined to keep Annabelle from wreaking more havoc, demonologists Ed and Lorraine Warren bring the possessed doll to the
locked artifacts room in their home, placing her “safely” behind sacred glass and enlisting a priest’s holy blessing.
But an unholy night of horror awaits as Annabelle awakens the evil spirits in the room, who all set
their sights on a new target—the Warrens' ten-year-old daughter, Judy, and her friends.
Judy Warren, played by Mckenna Grace.
Mary Ellen, played by Madison Iseman.
Daniela Rios, played by Katie Sarife.
Bob Palmeri, played by Michael Cimino.
Annabelle "Bee" Mullins, played by Samara Lee.
Lorraine Warren, played by Vera Farmiga.
Annabelle Comes Home is a 2019 American supernatural horror film written and directed by Gary Dauberman, in his
directorial debut, from a story by Dauberman and James Wan, who also served as producer with Peter Safran.
It serves as a sequel to 2014's Annabelle and 2017's Annabelle: Creation, and
as the sixth installment in The Conjuring Universe franchise.
The film stars Mckenna Grace, Madison Iseman, and Katie Sarife, along with Vera Farmiga
and Patrick Wilson, who reprise their roles as Ed and Lorraine Warren.
In early April 2018, Warner Bros.
Pictures announced that a then-untitled film in The Conjuring
Universe franchise would be released on July 3, 2019.
Later that month, it was announced that the film would be another installment in the Annabelle series, with Dauberman signed on
to write and direct the film in his directorial debut, based on a story treatment written by Dauberman and Wan.
Principal photography had begun by mid-October and was
finished in December 2018 in Los Angeles.
Annabelle Comes Home was theatrically released in the
United States on June 26, 2019, by Warner Bros.
Pictures and New Line Cinema.
It grossed $231.3 million worldwide and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of supernatural, halloween, babysitter, priest, doll.
The tone is dark.